So what's new, Mark? How is your new job going?
To be honest, I can't complain.
I really love the company that I am working for.
My co workers are all really friendly and helpful.
They really help me feel welcome.
It's a really energetic and fun atmosphere.
My boss is hilarious and he's
really flexible. Really?
How so? He allows me to
come in when I want and make my own hours.
I can also leave early if I start early.
There is no real dress code either.
I can wear jeans and a T shirt if I want.
I can even wear shorts in the summer.
Wow, it sounds really cool.
I can't stand wearing a suit every day.
Which do you prefer? Working late or finishing
early? I prefer finishing early.
I really enjoy the morning. I love
getting up early and going for a run.
There's nothing like watching the sunrise while drinking my morning
coffee. Really?
I am opposite. I love sleeping in.
I am most alert in the evenings. I'm a
real night owl.
Well, you know what they say. The early
bird catches the worm. You know, you could
be right. Maybe I will try to go to bed
a little earlier tonight.